[
   {
      "sQuestion":"what is Global Recovery rate of COVID-19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"around 80%",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "around 80%",
         "around 90%",
         "around 100%"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
	  "sQuestion":"How long does it take to develop symptoms after contracting COVID 19 ?",
	  "sAnswer":"upto 72 hour",
	  "sMultiOptions":[
		 "upto 72 hour",
		 "upto 4 hour",
		 "lessthan 24 hour"
	  ],
	  "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Does Antibiotic help in curing COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"No",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "No",
         "Yes",
         "Maybe"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Following is not symptom of covid 19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"Hair fall",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "fatigue",
         "difficulty in breathe",
         "Hair fall"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Recommended distance between people to avoid COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"Within 1-2m",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "less than 1m",
         "Within 1-2m",
         "close contact"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Whats does SARS stands for ?",
      "sAnswer":"Severe acute respiratory Syndrome",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Severe acute respiratory Syndrome",
         "Severe acute reverse Syndrome",
         "Severe agile respiratory Syndrome"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"what is COVID ?",
      "sAnswer":"Virus",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Virus",
         "Bacteria",
         "Fungus"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"which of the following animal is high susceptible to COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"CAT",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "CAT",
         "DONKEY",
         "HORSE"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Which is highly effected country in Europe due to COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"ITALY",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "ITALY",
         "FRANCE",
         "GERMANY"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"will weather play role in spread of COVID-19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"No",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Yes",
         "No",
         "Maybe"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"will weather play role in spread of COVID-19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"No",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Yes",
         "No",
         "Maybe"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Pick the right statement from following",
      "sAnswer":"Drinking Alcohol doesn't cure COVID-19",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Drinking Alcohol doesn't cure COVID-19",
         "Drinking Alcohol will cure COVID-19",
         "Drinking Alcohol will make sure we will not get COVID-19"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Pick the right statement from following",
      "sAnswer":"Thermal scanners cannot detect COVID-19",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Thermal scanners cannot detect COVID-19",
         "Thermal scanners will detect COVID-19",
         "Thermal scanners will detect and cure COVID-19"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Pick the right statement from following",
      "sAnswer":"Adding pepper to soup and meal will not help to prevent COVID-19",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Adding pepper to soup and meal will not help to prevent COVID-19",
         "Adding pepper to soup and meal will help to prevent COVID-19",
         "Adding pepper to soup and meal will help to cure COVID-19"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Pick the right statement from following",
      "sAnswer":"5G mobile network do not spread COVID-19",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "5G mobile network do not spread COVID-19",
         "5G mobile network will spread COVID-19",
         "5G mobile network will help grow COVID-19"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Pick the right statement from following",
      "sAnswer":"COVID 19 can be transmitted in areas with hot and humid climates",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "COVID 19 can be transmitted in areas with hot and humid climates",
         "COVID 19 cannot be transmitted in areas with hot and humid climates",
         "hot and humid climates kill COVID 19 virus"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Pick the right statement from following",
      "sAnswer":"Cold weather and snow cannot kill the COVID19 virus",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Cold weather and snow cannot kill the COVID19 virus",
         "Cold weather and snow can kill the COVID19 virus",
         "Cold weather and snow breed the COVID19 virus"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   }
]